Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VI: Yoshio Kishi's Files
  - Subseries D: Collecting
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - The Picture Postcard, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - Picture Postcards in the U.S., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Collecting - San Francisco, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Newsletters - The Photographic Collectors' Newsletter, vol. 1, no. 4, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters - The Photographic Collectors' Newsletter, vol. 2., no. 1, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters - The Photographic Collectors' Newsletter, vol. 2, no. 2, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters - The Photographic Collectors' Newsletter, vol. 2, no. 3, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Newsletters - Photographic Historical Society of New York, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Online Auctions - December 1998 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Online Auctions - January 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Online Auctions - January 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Online Auctions - February 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Online Auctions - February 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Online Auctions - March 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Online Auctions - March 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Online Auctions - April 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Online Auctions - April 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Online Auctions - March 1999 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Online Auctions - June 1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Online Auctions - July 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Online Auctions - July 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Online Auctions - August 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Online Auctions - August 1999 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Online Auctions - September 1999 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Online Auctions - October 1999 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Online Auctions - November 1999 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Online Auctions - December 1999 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Online Auctions - January 2000 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Online Auctions - February 2000 (1 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Online Auctions - February 2000 (2 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Online Auctions - February 2000 (3 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Online Auctions - March 2000 (1 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Online Auctions - March 2000 (2 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Online Auctions - March 2000 (3 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Online Auctions - April 2000 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Online Auctions - May 2000 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Online Auctions - June 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Online Auctions - June 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 46)
    - Online Auctions - July 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Online Auctions - July 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Online Auctions - August 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Online Auctions - August 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Online Auctions - September 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Online Auctions - September 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Online Auctions - October 2000 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Online Auctions - November 2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Online Auctions - December 2000 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Online Auctions - January 2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Online Auctions - February 2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Online Auctions - March 2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Online Auctions - April 2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Online Auctions - May 2001 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Online Auctions - June and July 2001 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Online Auctions - August, September, and October 2001 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Online Auctions - November 2001 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Online Auctions - December 2001 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Online Auctions - January 2002 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Online Auctions - February 2002 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Online Auctions - March 2002 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Online Auctions - April 2002 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Online Auctions - June and July 2002 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Online Auctions - August 2002 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Online Auctions - September 2002 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Online Auctions - October 2002 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Online Auctions - November and December 2002 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Online Auctions - 2003-2007 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Online Auctions - Miscellaneous documents, 1998-2002 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Photocopied prints, advertisements, and cartoons depicting Asian Americans, Undated (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Price Guides - Botanical and Horticultural Books, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Price Guides - Collectibles: The Nostalgia Collector's Bible, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Price Guides - The Official Overstreet Comic Book Price GUide, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Price Guides - The Official Price Guide: American Illustrated Art, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Price Guides - The Official Price Guide to Collectibles of the 50's and 60's, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Price Guides - The Official Price Guide to Science Fiction and Fantasy Collectibles, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Price Guides - The Official Price Guide to Star Trek and Star Wars Collectibles, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Price Guides - The Paperback Price Guide #2, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Price Guides - The Price Guide to Autographs, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Price Guides - The Price Guide to Autographs (interleaved paper), Undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Shipment 03, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Shipment 05, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Shipment 06, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Shipment 11, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Shipment 12, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Shipment 20, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Shipment 26, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Shipment 27, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Shipment 28, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Shipment 29, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Shipment 30, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Shipment 31, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Shipment 32 & 33, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Organizing
    - Card Catalog - Authors index, posters, photos, lithographs, filmography, scripts, directors, videocassettes, printing, bibliography, music, mixed, Undated (Box 71)
    - Card Catalog - Books on prostitution, bookseller cards, books: Sold and Do Not Have, Undated (Box 72)
    - Card Catalog - Silent Films: Actor index, Title index, Undated (Box 73)
    - Card Catalog - Sound Films: Alphabetical title index, Name index, Undated (Box 74)
    - Card Catalog - Sound Films: Chronological title index, Undated (Box 75)
    - Card Catalog - Subject cards, chronological publication index, microfiche, Undated (Box 76)
    - Quotes about silent film, Undated (Box 77)
  - Subseries F: Subject Files
    - Aaron's Postcards, Undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Abeel, David, Undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Abdullah, Achmed, Undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Adams, Henry, 1838-1918, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Advertising and Asian Americans, Undated (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Advertisements, Undated (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - African Americans, Undated (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - AFNY News Forum, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Agee, James, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Ahn, Philip, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Airplane Models, Undated (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Amerasia Journal, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Amerasia News, Undated (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - American Film Institute, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - American Museum of Natural History, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - "An Apple, An Orange", Undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Anti-Asian Violence, 1988-1990 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Anti-Chinese Movement, Undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Anti-Japanese Movement, Undated (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Appalachia, 1998-2011 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Appocalypse Now, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Arab-Americans, 1987, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Art Forgery, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Artists, Asian American, Undated (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Ashbery, John, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Asia, Early contacts with, Undated (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Asia in American Textbooks, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Asian American Actors, Undated (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Asian American Arts Alliance, 1997-1999, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Asian American Arts Centre, NYC, 1988-1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Asian American art exhibits, Undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Asian American Bookseller, Undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Asian American Center, Queens College, 1988-2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Asian American collections, 2003, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Asian American Curriculum Project, 1970, 1993-1996 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Legal Defence and Education Fund, NYC, 1987-1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Asian American Media Group, NY, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Asian American Network, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Asian American Organizations, 1988-1990, Undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Asian American Performing Artists (formerly Oriental Actors of America), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Asian American Repertory Theater, Undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Asian American Resource Workshop, Boston, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Asian American Spirit, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Asian American Studies, 1972, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Asian American Writers' Workshop, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Asian Americans for Equality, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Asian Americans for Fair Media, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Asian Americans in Films, Undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Asian Americans - Theater, Undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Asian Cinevision, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Asian Nail Salons, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Asian New Yorker, 1990-1991, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Asian Outlook, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Asian Pacific American Institute, 2008-2011 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Asians in Africa, 1972-1973 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Asians in America, Undated (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Asians in New York, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Asia Society, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Asian / Pacific American Heritage Festival, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Asian Voice, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Asians on the Alert, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Association for Asian American Studies (1 of 2), 1989-2000 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Association for Asian American Studies (2 of 2), 1993-1999 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Association for Asian American Performance, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Association for Asian American Performance, 1990, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Astrology, Asian, Undated (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Atomic Bomb, Undated (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Australia, Asians in, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Babb, Sandra, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Babcock, C.G., Reflections on Dependency..., Undated (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Baker, "The Concentration Camp Conspiracy", Undated (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - The Balch Institute for Ethnic Studies, 1973, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Baldwin, James, 2005 (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Baldwin, S.L., "Must the Chinese Go", 1886-1890 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Ballard, J.G., 2009, Undated (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Ballet, 2007-2010 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Balzac, Honore de, Undated (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Bancroft, Hubert Howe, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Basilisk, Undated (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Beacon Theater, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Beekman, Allan, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Belasco, David, Undated (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Bell, G. "The Golden Gate and the Silver Screen", 1984 (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - Bendiner, Robert, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Benjamin, Walter, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Bibliography, Undated (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Biggers, Earl Derr, 1973, Undated (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Bing, S., 1999 (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - "Black Dahlia", 2006 (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Black Face, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Black History, Undated (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Black Memorabilia, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Blake, William, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Bleiler, Everett F., Undated (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Bloodhound Gang, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Bluejackets with Perry in Japan, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Boat People, 1978, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Book Collections, 2000, 2007, Undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Book Sellers, 1996-2010 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Boorstin, Daniel J., 1876 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Bouguereau, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Boxer Movement, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Brides, Mail-Order, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Bridge Magazine, NYC, Undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Breillat, Catherine, 2008, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Brinkley, Capt. F., 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Brislin, Tom, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Brooks, Louise, 1979, 1998-1999, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Brownlow, Kevin, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Bryce, Lloyd "Dream of Conquest", 1889 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Buchwald, Art, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Buck, Pearl S. "Is There a Case for Foreign Missions?", 1933 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Buddhism, Undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Budo, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Buell, R.L. "Japanese Immigration", 1924 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Bulosan, Carlos, 1946, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Burke, Thomas, Undated (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Burlingame, Anson - Banquet, 1868 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Bushido, Undated (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Busing, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - CAAAV - Organizing Asian Communities, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - California, Chinese in, Undated (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - California, Japanese in, 1947, Undated (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Callahan, Harry, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Cambodia, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Campbell, Bartley, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Canada, Asians in, 1972, 1977, 1982, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Canes, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Cartoons, Undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Cavafy, C.P., 2009 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Chai, Winberg, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Chan, Charlie, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Chan, Charlie, Undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Chan is Missing, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Chang, K. "The Iron Moonhunter", 1977 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Charlie Chan, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Chen, Tina - "Betrayed into Motion", 1994 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Chinag Ching & Co Materials, Undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - A Child in Prison Camp, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Children's Books, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Chin, Frank, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - China, 1933-1992 (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - China and the West, Undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - China - Bibliography, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 49)
    - China, Books on, 1985-1988 (Box 33, Folder 50)
    - China (Business Ethics), 1995 (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - China, Christianity in, Undated (Box 33, Folder 52)
    - China - Film, 1972-1990 (Box 33, Folder 53)
    - China, Images of, Undated (Box 33, Folder 54)
    - China / Japan, Early books on, Undated (Box 33, Folder 55)
    - China Trade, 1982-1984 (Box 33, Folder 56)
    - China Trade, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 57)
    - China - Writers, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 58)
    - China, Writers on, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 59)
    - "Chinatown", 1974 (Box 33, Folder 60)
    - Chinatown, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 61)
    - Chinatown History Museum, 1989, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 62)
    - Chinatown in Fiction, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 63)
    - Chinatown, New York, Undated (Box 33, Folder 64)
    - Chinatown, New York - Photographs, Undated (Box 33, Folder 65)
    - Chinatown, Philadelphia, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 66)
    - Chinatown, San Francisco, 1940, Undated (Box 33, Folder 67)
    - Chinatown, Washington D.C., 1990 (Box 33, Folder 68)
    - Chinese Acrobats, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 69)
    - Chinese American History, Chronology of, Undated (Box 33, Folder 70)
    - Chinese Americans, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Chinese Criminal Activity, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Chinese, Early Immigrants, Undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Chinese in the United States, Undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Chinese Laundries, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Chinese Poet in New York, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Chinese surnames, Undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Chinese Theater, 1975, Undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Chinese view of the U.S., 1990 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Chinese American Planning Council, NYC, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Chinese Artists in New York, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Chinese Culture Foundation, San Francisco, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Chinese Historical Society of America, San Francisco, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Chinese in New York, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Chin, Frank, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Ching, Frank, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Chinoiserie, 1988, Undated (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Chiu, Tony, Undated (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Chronology, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Chu, Louis H., 1961 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Chu, R.J., Undated (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Chung, Sue Fawn, Undated (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Churches and Asian Americans, 1927 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Circus, Chinese, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Civil Rights, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Clark, Larry, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Clurman, Robert, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Coan, Mr. / Binyan, Lawrence, 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 27A)
    - Cohan, George M., 1973 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Aaron M. - correspondence, 1989-2004 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Coleman, A.D., 1999 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Collectors, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Collyers Brothers, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Color Lines, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Comics, 2008-2011 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Comics, 1974, 1988-1990, Undated (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Committee Against Anti-Asian Violence, 1989-2000 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - Contacts between East and West, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 38)
    - Cornell University - Asian American Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 39)
    - Cosmetology, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    - The Council on Interracial Books for Children, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    - Cowan, Robert Ernest, "Bibliography of the Chinese Question", 1909 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    - Cross Currents, UCLA, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 43)
    - Culin, Stewart, 1887 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    - Culver, R.K., 1918 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Curtin, Patricia A., 1995 (Box 34, Folder 46)
    - Cussler, Clive, 1990, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 47)
    - Dance, Asia in, 1930, 1987-1989, Undated (Box 34, Folder 48)
    - The Dance and the Railroad, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 49)
    - Daniels, R., "American Historians and East Asian Immigrants", 1974 (Box 34, Folder 50)
    - Davis, Horace - Chinese Immigration, 1878 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    - De Quincey, Thomas, 1981, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 52)
    - "The Deer Hunter", 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 53)
    - Demography, 1972, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    - Diary of an Official of the Bakufu, Undated (Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Dime Novel, 1974, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 56)
    - Doblen, Alfred, 1993, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 57)
    - Doi, Steven G., 1989 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    - Dooley, Roger, Undated (Box 34, Folder 59)
    - Dong, Arthur, Undated (Box 34, Folder 60)
    - Drama, Images of Chinese in, Undated (Box 34, Folder 61)
    - Drama, Images of Japanese in, Undated (Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Drugs, 1972-1973, Undated (Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Duus, Umezawa, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    - East West Players, Undated (Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Eating dogs, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Eaton, Allen H., 1962 (Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Economics, 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Education, 1988-1989 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Ellis, Henry, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 70)
    - An English-Chinese Phrase Book, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 71)
    - Ephemera, Undated (Box 34, Folder 72)
    - The Epistolarian, W.M. Hohri, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 73)
    - Ethnicity, 1972, 1975, 1988, Undated (Box 34, Folder 74)
    - Evacuation, Undated (Box 34, Folder 75)
    - Evacuation and Internment, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Evans, Henry - "Curious Lore of San Francisco's Chinatown", 1955 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Evil, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Executions and Torture, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Exhibitions, Undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Fales, William E.S. - "Bits of Broken China", 1902 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Fame (celebrity), 1993, 2002, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - "Farewell to Manzanar", 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Fiction, Asian American, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Fiction, Asian Americans in, 1951, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Fiction, China in, 1913, 1932, 1985, 1989, Undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Fiction, Japan in, 1911, 1913, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Fiction, Juvenile, Undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Filipinos in the U.S., Undated (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Film Archives, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Film, Asians in, 1921, Undated (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Film and History, Undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Film, Images of Chinese in, Undated (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Film, Images of Japanese in, 1989, Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Film Magazines, Undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Film Noir, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Film Pioneers and Grounbreakers 1894-1927, Undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Film Preservation, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Film, Silent, Undated (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Film, Sound, Undated (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Films, Asian American, 1975-1988 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Films, Images of Asians in, Undated (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Finck, H.T. - "The Pacific Coast Scenic Tour", 1890 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Fisk University, Undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Fitzgerals, O.P. - "California Sketches", 1896 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Flaubert, Gustave, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Fong, Benson, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Foot Binding, Undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Frost, J.B. - "California's Greatest Curse", 1879 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Fu Manchu, Undated (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Fujikawa, Gyo, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Fujimoto, Isao, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    - Fuller, Sam, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 38)
    - Fung, Richard, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Fung, Willie, Undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Gaddis, William, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Gaijin, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Gautier, Judith, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Gee, Helen, 1968, 1977, 1979, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 44)